hltv.org 2019-06-30

# HLTV.org - The home of competitive Counter-Strike

## Data controller:

HLTV.org ApS Aabogade 15 8200 Aarhus N Contact e-mail: hltv@hltv.org Cvr-nr. 37582999

## What information do we collect?

You cannot be a member of the site, if you don't give us a minimum of the information we need. We only collect your email, password and alias. You can at any given time withdraw your consent, by deleting or changing your information on your profile page. If you withdraw your consent, we will erase the personal information that you have provided us.

## Who is collecting the data and how do we collect the data?

HLTV.org collects the data when you type your information in the creation form and through browsers and cookies.

## Why do we collect the data?

We collect your email to verify you as a user and for recreating your password, if such a need should occur. We collect your IP, to avoid abuse of the page and to prevent any illegal actions. The personal data we collect through cookies is to adapt the content of HLTV.org specifically to you and for optimising HLTV.org. Your personal information will not be given to a third party. We do not use any sub-processor to handle your personal information.

## Your privacy rights and who to contact for insight to personal information.

If you want access to the information, that are registered about you at HLTV.org, you can see these on your profile page or contact hltv@hltv.org Is there any wrong information about you and you cannot correct them yourself or if you have any other objection towards the handling of your personal data, then contact us at hltv@hltv.org You have the possibility to get access to which information that is registered about you and you are entitled to object to our handling of your personal data. In case there should be any personal data that is wrong or misleading, then you are entitled to get them corrected. You can at any time object to information about you is made an object of handling, just write to us at hltv@hltv.org You can also at any given time withdraw your consent to the processing we use with your given consent. You have the right to complain about our handling of your personal information if we don't agree in your objections. The complaint is to be send to Datatilsynet. See more at [www.datatilsynet.dk](https://www.datatilsynet.dk/)

## Deletion of your personal information

We store your personal information as long as we have an active membership relationship with you. You can at any time remove the information associated with your membership profile and we will delete it immediately.

## Data portability

Your access to get your data retrieved can be found on your profile page.

## Our role as data processor

In relation to you we are the controllers for the personal information that you handle and store on HLTV.org.

## Change of our privacy policy

In case of any significant changes of this privacy policy, we will notify you of that in reasonable time with a visible note on our website. Latest revision May 2018.
